Guide to the Brooklyn Ephemera Collection BCMS.0007
Brooklyn Collection
- Portraits: Fulton, Robert (Box 12)
- Portraits: Griswold, Stephen (Box 12)
- Portraits: Lord Sterling (Alexander, William) (Box 12)
- Portraits: Macmonnies, Frederick W. (Box 12)
- Portraits: Moses, Robert (Box 12)
- Portraits: Roebling, John A. (Box 12)
- Portraits: Roebling, Washington A. (Box 12)
- Portraits: Vogel, William (Box 12)
- Postcards (Box 12)
- Post Office: "Facts and Figures of Your Brooklyn Post Office" (Box 12)
- Post Office: General (Box 12)
- Prospect Heights (Box 12)
- Prospect Park Alliance (Box 12)
- Public Health (Box 12)
- Queens Library: Queens Library Gallery Exhibition (Box 12)
- Railroads: Els (Box 12)
- Railroads: Long Island Railroad (Box 12)
- Railroads: Tickets (Box 12)
- Randall's Island (Box 12)
- Recreation & Leisure: Recreation Survey (Box 12)
- Red Hook (Box 12)
- Religious Life: Jehovah's Witnesses (Box 12)
- Religious Life: Judaism (Box 12)
- Restaurant and Food Industry [2 folders] (Box 12, Box OS 6)
- Restaurant and Food Industry: National Sausage Casing Dealer's Association (Box OS 3)
- Restaurants: Bogota Latin Bistro (Box 12)
- Restaurants: C'est La Vie Lounge (Box 12)
- Restaurants: Gage & Tollner (Box 12)
- Restaurants: Juniors (Box 12)
- Restaurants: Once Upon A Sundae (Box 12)
- Restaurants: Ridgewood. Wyckoff House (Box 16)
- Restaurants: The Imperial (Box 12)
- Schools: Adult: Brooklyn College (Box 12, Box 16)
- Schools: Adult: Brooklyn College of Pharmacy (Box 12)
- Schools: Adult: Brooklyn Law School (Box 12)
- Schools: Adult: Cathedral College of the Immaculate Conception (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: New York City College of Technology (City Tech) (Box OS 6)
- Schools: Adult: Kingsborough Community College (Box 13, Box OS 3)
- Schools: Adult: Long Island University (LIU) (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: Medgar Evers College (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: National Academy of Beauty Culture (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: Polytechnic Institute of NYU (formerly Polytechnic University) (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: Pratt Institute: General (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: Pratt Institute: Students & Faculty (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: St. Francis College (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: St. John's University [2 folders] (Box 13)
- Schools: Adult: St. Joseph's College (Box 13)
- Schools: Fundraising (Box 13)
- Schools: Non-Brooklyn (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Adelphi Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Andrew Jackson High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Engineering Institute (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Female Academy, Invitation, 1847 (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Friends School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Heights Seminary: Announcements [course listings], 1911-1912, 1919-1920 (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Heights Seminary: Club handbooks, 1920-1921, 1925-1926 (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Brooklyn Heights Seminary: The Triangle [annual], 1913 June,1915 December (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Clinton Avenue Institute (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Elementary: Community School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Elementary: Seventh Day Adventists Tri-Borough Elementary Schools (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Flatbush School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: German American Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Alexander Hamilton Vocational High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Bishop Ford High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Bishop Kearney High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Bishop McDonnell Memorial High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Boro Hall Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute (Box 16)
- Schools: Private: High School: Our Lady of Perpetual Help (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Sarah J. Hale Vocational High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Shore Road Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. Angela Hall Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. Augustine Diocesan High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. Edmund Preparatory High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. Francis Preparatory (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. Francis Xavier (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. James Commercial School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: St. Joseph's High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: High School: Most Holy Trinity High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Packer Collegiate Institute (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Polytechnic Preparatory Day School (Box 13, Box 16)
- Schools: Private: Rabbinical Seminary of America (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Yeshiva of Flatbush (Box 13)
- Schools: Private: Yeshiva Ohel Moshe (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: Grammar School No. 10 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: Grammar School No. 35 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: Grammar School No. 108 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. [130?] – Pupils' records (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 5 (Box 13, Box 16)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 19 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 20 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 25 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 44 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 73 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 77 & 78 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 92 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 103 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 107 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 139 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 161 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 167 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 202 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 216: Parents' Association (Box 16)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 222 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 233 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: Elementary: P.S. 396 (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: General (Box 13, Box 16)
- Schools: Public: High School: Abraham Lincoln (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Boys High School [3 folders] (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Brooklyn High School of Automotive Trades (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Brooklyn Technical High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Bushwick High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Central School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Correspondence (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Eastern District High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Erasmus Hall Academy (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Erasmus Hall High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Franklin K. Lane (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: George Westinghouse High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls' Commercial High School (Box 13)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Administrative Correspondence and notes (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Annual Stunt Contest programs (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Calvin Patterson Memorial (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Correspondence (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Course of study (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Dr. Felter Memorial Exercises (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: History [use photocopies folder] (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Programs (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Programs and Commencement (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Programs / invitations (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: Publications (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Girls High School: "Rota Sapientiae" (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: James Madison High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Lincoln High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Manual Training High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Midwood High School (Box 14, Box 16)
- Schools: Public: High School: New Utrecht High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Samuel J. Tilden High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Sheepshead Bay High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: High School: Thomas Jefferson High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: Francis Scott Key (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: I.S. 142: Stranahan Junior High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: I.S. 320: Jackie Robinson Intermediate School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: J.H.S. 062: Ditmas (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: J.H.S 252: Arthur S. Somers (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: J.H.S. 263: David Marcus Junior High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: P.S. 218 (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: P.S. 292 (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: Sands Junior High School (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: J.H.S./ I.H.S.: Simon F. Rothschild (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: M.S. 340 North Star Academy (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: M.S. 136 Charles O. Dewey [P.S. 136] (Box 14)
- Schools: Public: School District 15 (Box 14)
- Sea Gate (Box 14)
- Seals: Seal of the City of Brooklyn (Box 14)
- Seals: City of Williamsburgh (Box 14)
- Seals: Kings County Seal (Box 14)
- Sewage (Box 14)
- Sheepshead Bay (Box 14)
- Social Notes (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: ASPCA (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Caregivers Resources Committee (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Children's Aid Society (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Federation of Jewish Charities (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Home for the Aged (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Home for Aged Men (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Industrial School and Home for Destitute Children (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Brooklyn Teen Challenge (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Flatbush Boys Club (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Hebrew Educational Society (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Homes and Shelters: Brooklyn Hebrew Home and Hospital for the Aged (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Homes and Shelters: Congregational Home for the Aged (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Homes and Shelters: Graham Home for Old Ladies (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Homes and Shelters: Home for Destitute Children (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Homes and Shelters: Industrial Home for the Blind (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Juvenile Temperance Society (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: National League for Women's Service (Letter) (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Orphan Asylum Society of the City of Brooklyn (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Poor Peoples Campaign, 1968 (Box 16)
- Social Welfare: Royal Arcanum (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Settlement Houses Colony House (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Southern Relief Committee (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Towarzystwo Wzajemnej Pomocy – St. Malachowskiego (Box 14)
- Social Welfare: Young Women's Christian Association (Y.W.C.A.) (see Organizations: YWCA) (Box 14)
- Soldiers and Sailors Memorial Arch (Box 14)
- Sports: Baseball: Brooklyn Cyclones (Box 14, Box OS 3)
- Sports: Baseball: Brooklyn Dodgers (Box 14)
- Sports: Baseball: Brooklyn Players in National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum (Box 14)
- Sports: Baseball: Washington Park (Box 14)
- Sports: Basketball: Brooklyn Nets (Box 14)
- Sports: Brooklyn Ice Palace (Box 14)
- Sports: Cycling (Box 14)
- Sports: Gotham Girls Roller Derby (Box 14)
- Sports: Martial Arts (Box 14)
- Sports: Schaffer's Adonis Health Club (Box 14)
- Sports: Sheepshead Bay Race Track (Box 14)
- Sports: Sport Prospect (Box OS 3)
- Stores & Shops: A&P (Atlantic & Pacific) (Box 14)
- Stores & Shops: Abraham and Straus (Box 14, Box OS 6, Box 16)
- Stores & Shops: Charles Gomer's Sons (Box 14)
- Stores & Shops: General (Box 14)
- Stores & Shops: John Paret & Co. (Box 14)
- Stores & Shops: King's/A.H. King Co. (Box 14)
- Stores & Shops: Loeser's (Box 14)
- Stores & Shops: Martin's (Box 14)
- Streets (Box 15)
- Sunset Park (Box 15)
- Telephone Company: New York Telephone Company (Box 15)
- Temples and Synagogues: Congregation Ahavas Israel, H.E.A. of Greenpoint (Box 15)
- Temples and Synagogues: Congregation Beth Jehuda (Box 15)
- Temples and Synagogues: Congregation Sons of Judah (Box 15)
- Temples and Synagogues: General (Box 15)
- Temples and Synagogues: Naomi Lodge B'nai B'rith (Box 16)
- Temples and Synagogues: Union Temple (Box 15)
- Theaters (Box 15)
- Theaters: Kings Theaters (Box 15)
- Tourist Information (Box 15)
- Traffic (Box 15)
- Transit History (Box 15)
- Transportation: Brooklyn Union Ferry Co. (Box 15)
- Transportation: Brooklyn, Flatbush, and Coney Island Railway (Box 15)
- Transportation: Buses: Flatbush Avenue Line Ticket (Box 15)
- Transportation: Fulton St. "L", 1916 (Box 15)
- Transportation: General (Box 15)
- Transportation: IRT/Flushing Line, press release, 1950 (Box 15)
- Transportation: Manhattan Beach (Box 15)
- Transportation: Subway and bus maps (Box 15)
- Transportation: Trolleys (Box 15)
- Tunnels: Brooklyn Battery Tunnel (Box 15)
- Tunnels: Renderings (Box 15)
- United States Information Agency Press Kit (Box 15)
- Utilities: Brooklyn Edison Co. (Box 15)
- Utilities: Brooklyn Gas Light Co. (Box 15)
- Utilities: Brooklyn Union Gas Co. (Box 15)
- Utilities: Coney Island Sewage Treatment Works (Box 15)
- Utilities: Consolidated Edison (Box 15)
- Utilities: Edison Electric Illuminating Company (Box 15)
- Utilities: General (Box 15)
- Veterans (Box 15)
- Views: Aerial: USGS (Box 15)
- Wallabout Channel (Box 15)
- War: Civil War (Box 15)
- Wards Island (Box 15)
- Washington Monument (Box 15)
- Waterfront (Box 15, Box 16)
- Weeksville (Box 15, Box OS 6)
- Williamsburg (Box 15)
- World War I (Box 15)
- World War II (Box 15)
- Writers (see Arts: Literary) (Box 15)